
Problem Statement
    
An integer x is called a proper divisor of an integer y if x is a divisor of y and 1 <= x < y.
Let us denote as s(a) the sum of all proper divisors of a. An integer a is called almost perfect by k if |a-s(a)| <= k.
You are given ints left, right and k. Return the number of integers between left and right, inclusive, that are almost perfect by k.
Definition
    
Class:
AlmostPerfectNumber
Method:
count
Parameters:
int, int, int
Returns:
int
Method signature:
int count(int left, int right, int k)
(be sure your method is public)
    

Constraints
-
left will be between 2 and 1000, inclusive.
-
right will be between left and 1000, inclusive.
-
k will be between 0 and 1000, inclusive.
Examples
0)

    
2
10
1
Returns: 4
The following numbers between 2 and 10 are almost perfect by 1: 2 (s(2) = 1), 4 (s(4) = 3), 6 (s(6) = 6) and 8 (s(8) = 7).
1)

    
5
5
5
Returns: 1

2)

    
11
20
50
Returns: 10

This problem statement is the exclusive and proprietary property of TopCoder, Inc. Any unauthorized use or reproduction of this information without the prior written consent of TopCoder, Inc. is strictly prohibited. (c)2003, TopCoder, Inc. All rights reserved.