
Problem Statement
    
You are given a compressed word that is in one of the following three forms:
A single character 'A' or 'B'. In this case, the uncompressed word is equal to the compressed one.
A string formatted as "ST" (quotes for clarity), where S and T are each compressed words. To uncompress a word of this form, uncompress S and T and return their concatenation.
A string formatted as "(X,S)" (quotes for clarity), where X is a digit between 1 and 9, inclusive, and S is a compressed word. To uncompress a word of this form, uncompress S and return the concatenation of X copies of that uncompressed word.
For example, "(2,A(3,AB))" uncompresses to "AABABABAABABAB", and "A(2,B)" uncompresses to "ABB". The latter example is uncompressed as follows:
"A(2,B)" is in form 2, where S = "A" and T= "(2,B)". S is in form 1 so it's already uncompressed. Next, we uncompress T.
"(2,B)" is in form 3, where X = 2 and S = "B". S is in form 1 so it's already uncompressed. We concatenate 2 copies of it to get "BB".
We concatenate S and T from step 1 to get "ABB".
A maximal continuous sequence of the same letter in a word is called a block. For example, "AABAAABBBAA" contains 5 blocks: AA, B, AAA, BBB, and AA.
You are given a compressed word. Return the number of blocks in the uncompressed form of the word.
Definition
    
Class:
BlockCounter
Method:
countBlocks
Parameters:
string
Returns:
long long
Method signature:
long long countBlocks(string word)
(be sure your method is public)
    

Constraints
-
word will contain between 1 and 50 characters, inclusive.
-
word will contain only parenthesis '(', ')', digits '1'-'9', letters 'A' and 'B' and commas ','.
-
word will be formatted as described in the problems statement.
Examples
0)

    
"(2,A(3,AB))"
Returns: 12
The example from the problem statement.
1)

    
"A(1,A)A(5,AAA)"
Returns: 1
In this case the word uncompresses to a string of 18 'A'-s.
2)

    
"ABA(2,ABA)(3,ABA)"
Returns: 13

3)

    
"(3,(2,(1,AB)))B"
Returns: 12

This problem statement is the exclusive and proprietary property of TopCoder, Inc. Any unauthorized use or reproduction of this information without the prior written consent of TopCoder, Inc. is strictly prohibited. (c)2003, TopCoder, Inc. All rights reserved.